Labor Editorial Files 5693
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Baer Sketches - A-Airplanes-Dirigibus (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Baer Sketches - A-Airplanes-Dirigibus-Sketches (Box 8, Folder 44)
- Baer Sketches - A-Artists (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Baer Sketches - A-Artists (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Baer Sketches - A-Astronauts (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Baer Sketches - A-Athletes (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Baer Sketches - A-Attitudes (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Baer Sketches - A-Attitudes-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Baer Sketches - A-Auto (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Baer Sketches - Auto (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Baer Sketches - A-Auto-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Baer Sketches - B (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Baer Sketches - B-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Baer Sketches - B-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Baer Sketches - B-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Baer Sketches - Babies (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Baer Sketches - Babies-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Baer Sketches - B-Backs, Balloons, Bubbles, Bells (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Baer Sketches - B-Backs, Balloons, Bubbles, Bells (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Baer Sketches - Bands (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Baer Sketches - Bands (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Baer Sketches - Barbies (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Baer Sketches - Baseball (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Baer Sketches - Baseball (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Baer Sketches - Baseball (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Baer Sketches - Baseball-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Baer Sketches - Basketball (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Baer Sketches - Battleships (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Baer Sketches - Beaches-Seashore Resorts (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Baer Sketches - B-Beds (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Baer Sketches - Big Biz (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Baer Sketches - Big Biz-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Baer Sketches - Black & Whites (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Baer Sketches - Blacksmiths (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Baer Sketches - Blacksmiths-Sketches (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Baer Sketches - Boats (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Baer Sketches - Boats-Sketches (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Baer Sketches - Bowling (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Baer Sketches - Bowling-Sketches (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Baer Sketches - Boy Scouts (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Baer Sketches - Brides (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Baer Sketches - Bridges (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Baer Sketches - Bridges-Sketches (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Baer Sketches - Buildings (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Baer Sketches - Burdens (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Baer Sketches - Burdens-Sketches (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Baer Sketches - Burglars-Bandits (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Baer Sketches - Burglars-Bandits-Sketches (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Baer Sketches - Business Men (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Baer Sketches - Business Men-Sketches (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Baer Sketches - C (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Baer Sketches - C (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Baer Sketches - C (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Baer Sketches - C (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Baer Sketches - C (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Baer Sketches - C (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Baer Sketches - C-Sketches (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Baer Sketches - C - Sketches (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Baer Sketches - Cannibals - Cavemen (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Baer Sketches - Cannons see Guns (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Baer Sketches - Capitol - Wash, White House (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Baer Sketches - Capitol - Wash, White House (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Baer Sketches - Capitol - Washington, White House - Sketches (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Baer Sketches - Chalk - Crayon Blaudek (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Baer Sketches - C - Child Labor + China (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Baer Sketches - C - Child Labor + China (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Baer Sketches - C - Child Labor + China - Sketches (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Baer Sketches - C - Church - Chapel (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Baer Sketches - C - Circus - See Clowns, Acrobats, Balances, etc. (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Baer Sketches - C - Circus - see Clowns, Acrobats, Balances, etc. - Sketches (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Baer Sketches - C - Cities (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Baer Sketches - C - Cities - Sketches (Box 10, Folder 37)
- Baer Sketches - C - Cliffs - Bluffs (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Baer Sketches - C - Clowns - Jesters (Box 10, Folder 39)
- Collective Bargaining - Conventions (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Collective Bargaining - Conventions - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Colonial (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Common People (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Common People - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Composition (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Composition - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Congress (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Congress - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Cooperation (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Corn (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Court Room (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Cowboys (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Crowds (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Crowds - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Cupid (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Cupid - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 17)
- C - Cuts New Deal: Company Union - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 18)
- C - Cuts New Deal: Company Union (Box 11, Folder 19)
- D (Box 11, Folder 20)
- D (Box 11, Folder 21)
- D (Box 11, Folder 22)
- D (Box 11, Folder 23)
- D - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 24)
- D - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Dancing (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Dancing (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Death (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Death - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Devils (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Doctors (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Doctors - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Dreams - Spirits (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Dredges - Derricks (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Dredges and Derricks - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Drunks (Box 11, Folder 36)
- E (Box 11, Folder 37)
- E (Box 11, Folder 38)
- E - Sketches (Box 11, Folder 39)
- E - Egypt (Box 11, Folder 40)
- E - Expressions (Box 11, Folder 41)
- E - Elections (Box 12, Folder 1)
- E - Elections - Sketches (Box 12, Folder 2)
- F (Box 12, Folder 3)
- F (Box 12, Folder 4)
- F (Box 12, Folder 5)
- F - Sketches (Box 12, Folder 6)
- F - Fables - Parables (Box 12, Folder 7)
- F - Fables - Parables - Sketches (Box 12, Folder 8)
- F - Factories (Box 12, Folder 9)
- F - Farmer - Farming (Box 12, Folder 10)
- F - Farmer - Farming (Box 12, Folder 11)
- F - Family - (Table) (Box 12, Folder 12)
- F - Family (table) (Box 12, Folder 13)
- F - Farmer - Farming (Box 12, Folder 14)
- F - Farmer - Farming (Box 12, Folder 15)
- F - Farmer - Farming (Box 12, Folder 16)
- F - Farmer - Sketches (Box 12, Folder 17)
- F - Father (Box 12, Folder 18)
- F - Fights (Box 12, Folder 19)
- F - Firemen (Box 12, Folder 20)
- F - Firemen (Box 12, Folder 21)
- F - Firemen - Sketches (Box 12, Folder 22)
- F - Fishing (Box 12, Folder 23)
- F - Flags (Box 12, Folder 24)
- F - Flags - Sketches (Box 12, Folder 25)
- F - Flowers (Box 12, Folder 26)
- F - Foot - Feet (Box 12, Folder 27)
- F - Football (Box 12, Folder 28)
- F - Football - F - (Box 12, Folder 29)
- F - Forts (Box 12, Folder 30)
- F - Furniture (Box 12, Folder 31)
- G (Box 12, Folder 32)
- G (Box 12, Folder 33)
- G (Box 12, Folder 34)
- G (Box 12, Folder 35)
- G - General (Box 12, Folder 36)
- G - Sketches (Box 12, Folder 37)
- G - General (Box 13, Folder 1)
- G - General - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 2)
- G- Giants (Box 13, Folder 3)
- G - Giants - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 4)
- G - Goddesses (Box 13, Folder 5)
- G - Goddesses - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 6)
- G - Golf (Box 13, Folder 7)
- G - Graph + Charts (Box 13, Folder 8)
- G - Graph + Charts - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 9)
- G - Graves (Box 13, Folder 10)
- G - Guns (Box 13, Folder 11)
- H (Box 13, Folder 12)
- H (Box 13, Folder 13)
- H (Box 13, Folder 14)
- H (Box 13, Folder 15)
- H (Box 13, Folder 16)
- H (Box 13, Folder 17)
- H (Box 13, Folder 18)
- H (Box 13, Folder 19)
- H - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 20)
- H - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 21)
- H - Hands (Box 13, Folder 22)
- H - Hands (Box 13, Folder 23)
- H - Hands (Box 13, Folder 24)
- H - Hands - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 25)
- H - Harvest (Box 13, Folder 26)
- H - Head (Box 13, Folder 27)
- H - High Cost of Living (Box 13, Folder 28)
- H - High Cost of Living - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 29)
- H - Hitler (Box 13, Folder 30)
- H - Hitler (Box 13, Folder 31)
- H - Hitler - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 32)
- H - Hobos (Box 13, Folder 33)
- H - Holidays - Armistice Day (Box 13, Folder 34)
- H - Holidays - Christmas (Box 13, Folder 35)
- H - Holidays - Christmas (Box 13, Folder 36)
- H - Holidays - Christmas (Box 13, Folder 37)
- H - Holidays - Christmas (Box 13, Folder 38)
- H - Holidays - Christmas - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 39)
- H - Holidays - Christmas - Sketches (Box 13, Folder 40)
- H - Holidays - Christmas Cartoons (Box 14, Folder 1)
- H - Holidays - Christmas Cartoons (Box 14, Folder 2)
- H - Holidays - Christmas Cartoons - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 3)
- H - Holidays - Easter (Box 14, Folder 4)
- H - Holidays - Fourth of July (Box 14, Folder 5)
- H - Holidays - Fourth of July - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 6)
- H - Holidays - Halloween (Box 14, Folder 7)
- H - Holidays - Halloween - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 8)
- H - Holidays - Lent (Box 14, Folder 9)
- H - Holidays - Mother's Day (Box 14, Folder 10)
- H - Holidays - New Years (Box 14, Folder 11)
- H - Holidays - New Years (Box 14, Folder 12)
- H - Holidays - New Years (Box 14, Folder 13)
- H - Holidays - New Years - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 14)
- H - Holidays - Thanksgiving (Box 14, Folder 15)
- H - Holidays - Thanksgiving (Box 14, Folder 16)
- H - Holidays - Thanksgiving - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 17)
- H - Holidays - Valentines (Box 14, Folder 18)
- H - Homes (Box 14, Folder 19)
- H - Homes (Box 14, Folder 20)
- H - Homes - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 21)
- H - Hunting Season (Box 14, Folder 22)
- I (Box 14, Folder 23)
- I - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 24)
- I - Ideas (Box 14, Folder 25)
- I - Ideas - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 26)
- I - Illustrations (Box 14, Folder 27)
- I - Indians (Box 14, Folder 28)
- I - Indians (Box 14, Folder 29)
- I - Inventions, Irish, Income Tax (Box 14, Folder 30)
- I - Inventions, Irish, Income Tax (Box 14, Folder 31)
- I - Inventions, Irish, Income Tax (Box 14, Folder 32)
- I - Inventions, Irish, Income Tax - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 33)
- J (Box 14, Folder 34)
- J (Box 14, Folder 35)
- J (Box 14, Folder 36)
- J (Box 14, Folder 37)
- J (Box 14, Folder 38)
- J - Sketches (Box 14, Folder 39)
- J-Judges, July, Justice (Box 15, Folder 1)
- J-Jury, Judges, Justice (Box 15, Folder 2)
- J-Judges, Jury, Justice - Sketches (Box 15, Folder 3)
- J-June (see wedding) (Box 15, Folder 4)
- K (Box 15, Folder 5)
- K (Box 15, Folder 6)
- K-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 7)
- K-Kids (Box 15, Folder 8)
- K-Kids (Box 15, Folder 9)
- K-Kids (Box 15, Folder 10)
- K-Kids (Box 15, Folder 11)
- K-Kids (Box 15, Folder 12)
- K-Kids-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 13)
- K-King (Box 15, Folder 14)
- K-King-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 15)
- K-Knights (Box 15, Folder 16)
- K-Knights-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 17)
- L (Box 15, Folder 18)
- L (Box 15, Folder 19)
- L (Box 15, Folder 20)
- L-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 21)
- L-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 22)
- L (Box 15, Folder 23)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 24)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 25)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 26)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 27)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 28)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 29)
- L-Labor-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 30)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 31)
- L-Labor (Box 15, Folder 32)
- L-Labor in Colors (Box 15, Folder 33)
- L-Labor-Sketches (Box 15, Folder 34)
- L-Labor in colors (Box 16, Folder 1)
- L-Lettering (Box 16, Folder 2)
- L-Lettering (Box 16, Folder 3)
- L-Liberty (Box 16, Folder 4)
- L-Liberty (Box 16, Folder 5)
- L-Liberty-Sketches (Box 16, Folder 6)
- L-Little Girls (Box 16, Folder 7)
- L-Little Girls-Sketches (Box 16, Folder 8)
- L-Lovers (Box 16, Folder 9)
- L-Men with last name (Box 16, Folder 10)
- L-Men with last name (Box 16, Folder 11)
- L-Men with last name (Box 16, Folder 12)
- L-Men with last name-Sketches (Box 16, Folder 13)
- M (Box 16, Folder 14)
- M (Box 16, Folder 15)
- M (Box 16, Folder 16)
- M (Box 16, Folder 17)
- M (Box 16, Folder 18)
- M (Box 16, Folder 19)
- M-Sketches (Box 16, Folder 20)
- M-March & May-Sketches (Box 16, Folder 21)
- M-March & May (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Majorettes (Box 16, Folder 23)
- maps (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Maps (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Maps-Sketches (Box 16, Folder 26)
- M-Mechanical (Box 16, Folder 27)
- M-Memorial Day (Box 16, Folder 28)
- M-Men (Box 16, Folder 29)
- M-Men (Box 16, Folder 30)
- M-Men-Sketches (Box 16, Folder 31)
- M-Men whose last name begins (Box 16, Folder 32)
- M-Men whose last name begins (Box 16, Folder 33)
- M-Mexico (Box 16, Folder 34)
- M-Miners (Box 16, Folder 35)
- M-Ministers, Monks (Box 16, Folder 36)
- M-Modern (Box 16, Folder 37)
- L-Lincoln: P-Prominent People (Box 19, Folder 1)
- M-Mountains (Box 17, Folder 1)
- M-Movies (Box 17, Folder 2)
- L-Lincoln -Sketches: P-Prominent People (Box 19, Folder 2)
- M-Music (Box 17, Folder 3)
- P-Prominent People - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 3)
- P-Prominent People - Lincoln (Box 19, Folder 4)
- M-People whose last name begins (Box 17, Folder 4)
- P-Prominent People - more Presidents (Box 19, Folder 5)
- M-People whose last name begins (Box 17, Folder 5)
- P-Prominent People-Rockefeller (Box 19, Folder 6)
- M-People whose last name begins (Box 17, Folder 6)
- N (Box 17, Folder 7)
- P-Prominent People-Roosevelt (Box 19, Folder 7)
- P-Prominent People-Roosevelt - Sketches (Box 19, Folder 8)
- N (Box 17, Folder 8)
- N (Box 17, Folder 9)
- P-Prominent People-Roosevelt (Box 19, Folder 9)
- N-Sketches (Box 17, Folder 10)
- P-Prominent People-Roosevelt (Box 19, Folder 10)
- N-Sketches (Box 17, Folder 11)
- P-Prominent People-Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 11)
- N-Nations (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Prominent People - Miscellaneous (Box 19, Folder 12)
- N-Nations (Box 17, Folder 13)
- P-Prominent People - Taft (Box 19, Folder 13)
- N-Nations (Box 17, Folder 14)
- P-Prominent People - Taft - Sketches (Box 19, Folder 14)
- N-Nations (Box 17, Folder 15)
- P-Prominent People - Truman (Box 19, Folder 15)
- N-Nations (Box 17, Folder 16)
- P-Prominent People -Truman (Box 19, Folder 16)
- N-Nations - Sketches (Box 17, Folder 17)
- P-Prominent People -Truman - Sketches (Box 19, Folder 17)
- N-Newspaper (Box 17, Folder 18)
- P-Prominent People -Wallace (Box 19, Folder 18)
- N-Nixon (Box 17, Folder 19)
- P-Pugilists (Box 19, Folder 19)
- N-Nixon - Sketches (Box 17, Folder 20)
- P-Pugilists (Box 19, Folder 20)
- NRA - Blouse Industry Code (Box 17, Folder 21)
- P-Pugilists (Box 19, Folder 21)
- NRA - Blouse Industry Code (Box 17, Folder 22)
- P-Pugilists - Sketches (Box 19, Folder 22)
- O (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Q (Box 19, Folder 23)
- O (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Q - Sketches (Box 19, Folder 24)
- R (Box 19, Folder 25)
- O-Sketches (Box 17, Folder 25)
- R (Box 19, Folder 26)
- O-Old age (Box 17, Folder 26)
- R (Box 19, Folder 27)
- O-Old age - Sketches (Box 17, Folder 27)
- R (Box 19, Folder 28)
- O-Old Times (Box 17, Folder 28)
- O-Old Times -Sketches (Box 17, Folder 29)
- R (Box 19, Folder 29)
- R (Box 19, Folder 30)
- P (Box 17, Folder 30)
- P (Box 17, Folder 31)
- R (Box 19, Folder 31)
- P (Box 17, Folder 32)
- R (Box 19, Folder 32)
- R-Sketches (Box 19, Folder 33)
- P (Box 17, Folder 33)
- R-Radio (Box 19, Folder 34)
- P (Box 17, Folder 34)
- R-Radio-Sketches (Box 19, Folder 35)
- P (Box 17, Folder 35)
- R-Rails (Box 19, Folder 36)
- P (Box 17, Folder 36)
- P (Box 17, Folder 37)
- P (Box 18, Folder 1)
- P (Box 18, Folder 2)
- P-Sketches (Box 18, Folder 3)
- P-Parades (Box 18, Folder 4)
- P-Parades - Sketches (Box 18, Folder 5)
- P-P- (Box 18, Folder 6)
- P-Pioneers (Box 18, Folder 7)
- P-Pirates (Box 18, Folder 8)
- P-Poker (Box 18, Folder 9)
- P-Policemen (Box 18, Folder 10)
- P-Politicians (Box 18, Folder 11)
- P-Poor - Poverty (Box 18, Folder 12)
- P-Posters (Box 18, Folder 13)
- P-Progress (Box 18, Folder 14)
- P-Prominent People - Characters (Box 18, Folder 15)
- P-Prominent People - Caricatures (Box 18, Folder 16)
- P-Prominent People - Caricature (Box 18, Folder 17)
- P-Prominent People - Characters (Box 18, Folder 18)
- P-Prominent People - Caricatures - Sketches (Box 18, Folder 19)
- P-Prominent People - Christ (Box 18, Folder 20)
- P-Prominent People - Coolidge (Box 18, Folder 21)
- P-Prominent People - D (Box 18, Folder 22)
- P-Prominent People - D - Sketches (Box 18, Folder 23)
- P-Prominent People - E (Box 18, Folder 24)
- P-Prominent People - Eisenhower (Box 18, Folder 25)
- P-Prominent People - Eisenhower - Sketches (Box 18, Folder 26)
- P-Prominent People - F (Box 18, Folder 27)
- P-Prominent People - G (Box 18, Folder 28)
- P-Prominent People - G - Sketches (Box 18, Folder 29)
- P-Prominent People - Humphrey (Box 18, Folder 30)
- P-Prominent People - Johnson (Box 18, Folder 31)
- P-Prominent People - Johnson - Sketches (Box 18, Folder 32)
- P-Prominent People - K- Kennedys (Box 18, Folder 33)
- P-Prominent People - K- Kennedys (Box 18, Folder 34)
- R-Railroads - Sketches (Box 20, Folder 1)
- R-Railroad Boys - Sketches (Box 20, Folder 2)
- R-Railroad Boys (Box 20, Folder 3)
- R-Railroad Boys (Box 20, Folder 4)
- R-Railroads (Box 20, Folder 5)
- R-Railroads (Box 20, Folder 6)
- R-Rich and Restaurants (Box 20, Folder 7)
- R-Rich and Restaurants - Sketches (Box 20, Folder 8)
- R-Rockets (Box 20, Folder 9)
- R-Rockets - Sketches (Box 20, Folder 10)
- R-Runways and Roads (Box 20, Folder 11)
- S (Box 20, Folder 12)
- S (Box 20, Folder 13)
- S (Box 20, Folder 14)
- S (Box 20, Folder 15)
- S (Box 20, Folder 16)
- S (Box 20, Folder 17)
- S (Box 20, Folder 18)
- S (Box 20, Folder 19)
- S (Box 20, Folder 20)
- S (Box 20, Folder 21)
- S (Box 20, Folder 22)
- S - Sketches (Box 20, Folder 23)
- S-Sailors (Box 20, Folder 24)
- S-Schools (Box 20, Folder 25)
- S-Schools - Sketches (Box 20, Folder 26)
- S-Scientists (Box 20, Folder 27)
- S-Seasons (Box 20, Folder 28)
- S-Seasons - Fall (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Seasons - Spring - April (Box 21, Folder 2)
- S-Seasons - Spring, April - Sketches (Box 21, Folder 3)
- S-Seasons - Spring (House Cleaning, Lovers, Wedding) (Box 21, Folder 4)
- S-Seasons - Spring (House Cleaning, Lovers, Wedding) - Sketches (Box 21, Folder 5)
- S-Seasons - Spring (House Cleaning, Lovers, Wedding) - Sketches (Box 21, Folder 6)
- S-Seasons - Winter (Box 21, Folder 7)
- S- Senator Sounder (Box 21, Folder 8)
- S-Sick (Box 21, Folder 9)
- S-Silhouette (Box 21, Folder 10)
- S-Silhouette (Designs) (Box 21, Folder 11)
- S-Society (Box 21, Folder 12)
- S-Soldier '60-'66 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- S-Soldiers in Uniform (Box 21, Folder 14)
- S-South America, Scotch, Spanish (Box 21, Folder 15)
- S-Speakers (Box 21, Folder 16)
- S-Sports (Box 21, Folder 17)
- S-Statues (Box 21, Folder 18)
- S-Stevenson (Box 21, Folder 19)
- S-Stores + Shops (Box 21, Folder 20)
- S- Storms (Box 21, Folder 21)
- S - Street Cars (Box 21, Folder 22)
- S- Supreme Court (Box 21, Folder 23)
- S-Swimming (Box 21, Folder 24)
- S-Symbolic (Box 21, Folder 25)
- Symbolic - Sketches (Box 21, Folder 26)
- T (Box 21, Folder 27)
- T (Box 21, Folder 28)
- T (Box 21, Folder 29)
- T (Box 21, Folder 30)
- T - Sketches (Box 21, Folder 31)
- T - Tanks (Box 21, Folder 32)
- T-Technique (Box 21, Folder 33)
- T-Technique - Sketches (Box 21, Folder 34)
- T-Television (Box 21, Folder 35)
- T-Tennis (Box 21, Folder 36)
- T-Theatres (Box 21, Folder 37)
- T-Traffic Taxi (Box 21, Folder 38)
- T-Travel (Box 21, Folder 39)
- T-Trees (Box 21, Folder 40)
- T-Trees (Box 21, Folder 41)
- U (Box 22, Folder 1)
- U (Box 22, Folder 2)
- U - Sketches (Box 22, Folder 3)
- U-UN (Box 22, Folder 4)
- U-Uncle Sam (Box 22, Folder 5)
- U-Uncle Sam (Box 22, Folder 6)
- U-Uncle Sam (Box 22, Folder 7)
- U-Uncle Sam - Sketches (Box 22, Folder 8)
- V (Box 22, Folder 9)
- V (Box 22, Folder 10)
- V (Box 22, Folder 11)
- V - Sketches (Box 22, Folder 12)
- V - Vacations (Box 22, Folder 13)
- V - Voting, Victory (Box 22, Folder 14)
- V - Voting, Victory - Sketches (Box 22, Folder 15)
- W (Box 22, Folder 16)
- W (Box 22, Folder 17)
- W (Box 22, Folder 18)
- W (Box 22, Folder 19)
- W (Box 22, Folder 20)
- W (Box 22, Folder 21)
- W (Box 22, Folder 22)
- W-Sketches (Box 22, Folder 23)
- W-Sketches (Box 22, Folder 24)
- W-War (Box 22, Folder 25)
- W-War - Sketches (Box 22, Folder 26)
- W - War - Soldiers in Color (Box 22, Folder 27)
- W - War - Soldiers in Color (Box 22, Folder 28)
- War - Soldiers in color (Box 23, Folder 1)
- W-G. Washington (Box 23, Folder 2)
- W - G. Washington (Box 23, Folder 3)
- W - G. Washington - sketches (Box 23, Folder 4)
- W - West (Box 23, Folder 5)
- W - Wheat (Box 23, Folder 6)
- W- Wife (Box 23, Folder 7)
- W - Women (Box 23, Folder 8)
- W - Women - Sketches (Box 23, Folder 9)
- W - Women (Baer) (Box 23, Folder 10)
- W - Women (Baer) - Sketches (Box 23, Folder 11)
- W - Women Glamour (Box 23, Folder 12)
- W - Women in Glamour (Box 23, Folder 13)
- W- Women Glamour, Sketches (Box 23, Folder 14)
- W- Women in Cartoons (Box 23, Folder 15)
- W- Women in Cartoons - Sketches (Box 23, Folder 16)
- W- Women in color (Box 23, Folder 17)
- W - Women in color (Box 23, Folder 18)
- W - Woodrow Wilson (Box 23, Folder 19)
- W - Woodrow Wilson (Box 23, Folder 20)
- W - World (Box 23, Folder 21)
- W - World - Sketches (Box 23, Folder 22)
- W - World War I - 1917 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- W- World War I - Sketches (Box 23, Folder 24)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- W - World War II, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- W - World War II - Sketches, 1941 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- X-Y-Z (Box 23, Folder 34)
- John Baer - Sketches - Misc. (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Misc. Sketches (Box 23, Folder 36)
- John Baer Sketches - Misc. (Box 23, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 38)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 1)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 2)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 3)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 4)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 5)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 6)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 7)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 8)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 9)
- John Baer - Scrapbook - North Dakota + Bismark Boosters (Box 24, Folder 10)
- John Baer - Scrapbook Baerfacts + Diary of a New Senator + Others (Box 24, Folder 11)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 12)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 13)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 14)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 15)
- John Baer - Scrapbook (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Misc. Associated Press Story (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Misc. - Kerns (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Misc. - Kerns (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous - "A New Day for Blacks" (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Miscellaneous - Rail Boys (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous - Union Label, Poem about "Rube" and Forum (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Miscellaneous - Union Label, Poem about "Rube" and Forum (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Aesop's Fables, 1934 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Twenty Fourth Annual Report of the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1910 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Scrapbook, 1918 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Cartoons (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Book of Clip Art (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Book of Post Cards (Box 25, Folder 7)